The Disastrous Life of Saiki K.
From the way you carry yourself,
It's quite clear you're not like other people
You smiled shyly at me
Before quietly averting your gaze
I made a rule for myself
Letting me tell little white lies
But you saw right through me
And you should know
That I know that you know
I don't want to hurt you
But I want to know more about you
The truth is always there
Lurking in the depths of our eyes
I don't want to get hurt
But I want you to know more about me
Your youth is no disaster
So look me in the eyes
A Genius Magician!? Uryoku Chouno
Amazing!
It's time for a super magic show by the miraculous illusionist Uryoku Chouno!
Hey, you over there! You can watch too!
You'll see some amazing miracles!
No thanks. I've already seen through them.
Oh, you're a skeptic, are you?
Well, once you've seen my amazing show, you'll be completely enthralled!
If he really wants me to watch, why not.
Okay! I've got an ordinary box here.
No...
It isn't ordinary.
Of course, there's nothing inside.
Well, the partition would be hidden from this angle.
However, once I do this... it's party time!
Amazing!
So what do you think, kid?! Amazing, isn't it?
More like "no amazing."
And just when are you going to use that dove?
Now for today's main event!
My most amazing trick. It's super illusion time!
My assistant Michael will teleport from one box to another!
Come on, Michael!
He seems more like a "Mr. Ike" than "Michael."
Now, Michael has entered the box!
Drumroll, start!
He makes the sound himself?
I wonder how he's gonna move...
This is exciting.
At a time like this, what kind of face should I make?
It hurts to see him so self-confident.
But I'm more worried about...
...this guy.
Well then, let's open the box!
Hey, now. Michael hasn't gotten there yet.
Three! Two! One!
It's party time!
Amazing!
At times like these, what kind of face does someone make?
Perhaps a face like this?
Geez, give me a break, Mr. Ike!
Don't blame me. You gave the signal too early.
Now, give me 500 yen for helping you.
No one tipped me, so I don't have any money for you this time, geez.
Oh? You're still here?
What? Oh, a tip?
Don't worry about it.
I can't take money from a child like—
Piiko!
I completely forgot about her.
Who would forget about a dove in their own hat?
How did you know I had a dove in my hat anyway?
Don't tell me...
You want to be an illusionist?!
That's how you figured it out, huh?
Well, I guess I'll leave it at that.
My show today must have looked pretty pathetic to you, huh?
Maybe I'm not suited for this work after all.
I was just your typical office worker up until several months ago.
But I made a little blunder.
Oh, crap.
So I got laid off.
And immediately after I lost my job, my wife left me.
I should've left when I had the chance.
I couldn't pay rent, so I was kicked out of my house too.
With that one mistake, everything disappeared: my job, my wife, my house.
Then I thought, "That's right, I'll be an illusionist!"
What were you thinking?
So many things had disappeared before me,
maybe I had a talent for making things "disappear"!
Your reasoning is seriously flawed.
So I turned down my new job offer,
and debuted on the street as an illusionist!
Again, what were you thinking?
If I save up 1.2 million yen with my shows and buy the magic body sawing box,
my wife will definitely take me back!
I wouldn't be so sure.
Maybe I made the wrong choice after all.
Talk about getting off track.
He should quit this illusionist stint and get a real job.
Oops. Sorry for all the gloomy talk.
But what would convince him to quit?
Oh, yeah! You want to be an illusionist too, right?
Want me to judge your technique?
That's it!
Ooh. You're going to pull something out of your bag?
If I show the gulf between our skills with an incredible illusion, he'll likely drop his act.
RUMBLE
What're you going to pull out? A dove?
You should know I can bring out a bowling ball.
fwooh
Seriously?!
This is when you're supposed to say "Amazing!"
This should be enough to discourage him.
Thank you. You've opened my eyes.
If your talent was long, flowing hair, mine would be an eyelash.
I now know the gulf between our skills.
The hair metaphor was weird, but now it should all—
Please take me as your apprentice!
I should have guessed...
Second Encounter (on TV)! Uryoku Chouno
I do like TV.
I would give my life for you.
But you don't like nam pla ramen, do you?
TV is a way for me to experience surprise and excitement.
This is because I can't hear the thoughts of the actors on the screen.
Well, I think a mystery drama is about to start on this channel.
Tonight, you will witness a miraculous feat!
That miraculous feat will be brought to you by the formerly homeless distinctive illusionist, Uryoku Chouno!
Amazing!
See? Proof positive that TV can surprise me.
He became an illusionist after losing everything,
and he'll perform a grand, miraculous illusion tonight!
This is hard to believe, though.
When I first met him, he almost killed his dove.
To think that he's improved enough to appear on TV...
What I have in store this time is a miraculous escape!
Hold on, can he handle this? And this is a live broadcast.
Well, it's a TV show, so he'll probably be fine, right?
The show is finally about to start!
Mr. Chouno's hands and feet are bound. And he's now getting inside the box!
Oops! He fell!
I think he'll be fine, but...
Mr. Chouno is now inside the box!
His assistant, the also formerly homeless Mr. Michael, closes the door!
Oh, hey, wai—
It's now closed!
He said, "Oh, hey, wai—" right before the door shut.
And he's banging on the door really hard.
He needs to escape within five minutes if he doesn't want to be destroyed along with the box!
And now to start the countdown!
Can he really pull this off?
There are now less than three minutes left!
What should I do?
I guess it doesn't matter. If you think about it,
I'm not close enough to jump in and save him anyway.
There are two minutes remaining!
Hold on a sec. What happens if he fails?
There's been a huge accident! This wasn't supposed to happen!
Is Mr. Chouno okay?!
We will continue our coverage until the very end!
That's unacceptable!
It would cut into the mystery drama I want to watch.
I can teleport to the performance site,
but I must not appear on TV.
Okay. There's exactly one place where the camera will never catch me.
Right inside the box.
Don't worry. You can stop banging on the door.
I'll get you out right—
All right! So far, so good.
I was able to escape without a hitch.
The staging to make it appear as if I'm inside is working too.
So he really has improved.
Five minutes have finally passed!
Mr. Michael will now insert the swords!
What am I gonna do?
I can't just teleport out.
I have to wait three minutes to teleport again.
Seventeen swords remain!
Unbelievable.
Now, this is the last sword!
Is he really all right?!
No one could be all right after this... except me.
I dislocated all sorts of joints, ugh.
What's next?
Next up is the crane!
The box is raised thirty meters high, and...
...dropped!
The way to avoid injury in this situation...
...is to...
...jump at this instance.
Piece of cake.
The box now is in terrible shape due to the shock from the drop!
But it doesn't end here, folks!
Now we will bathe it in fire!
Good grief, I can't even catch my breath.
But given all the hot weather recently,
I'm well-prepared for heatstroke.
And to finish it up, we're using...
There's more?
...a road roller!
The box is no longer intact!
What has become of Mr. Chouno?!
Whoa! What's that?!
Mr. Chouno has made a sudden appearance!
Amazing!
His escape was a complete success!
Good grief. My escape was a complete success too. Sheesh.
Good thing the soil was soft.
I know I said that TV is a source of surprise and excitement for me,
but this wasn't what I had in mind.
Well, that concludes today's "Miraculous Magic Show"!
Amazing!
Guess I'll go home and watch the drama now.
Well then, I have an announcement to make.
You have the sun's fragrance...
The drama Love Fantasy is on just after this, at 10 o'clock.
It's a thrilling tale in which a man tries to find the truth behind his girlfriend's mysterious death.
You have the sun's fragrance...
I bet no one will figure out that I'm the killer.
Be sure to tune in!
No thanks.
How Shady! Dark Reunion!
To tell you the truth, I've been summoned.
I cannot yet elaborate, but just know we're on the cusp of a sea change.
When the time is right, I will fill you in, Saiki.
Oh? Did he make a friend or something?
Thurisaz, isa, hagalaz.
Sowilo, gebo, fehu.
Eihwaz.
So you've come.
I hope you haven't been followed, The Jet-Black Wings.
Not to worry, Jade Eyes. I made sure of it.
Hold! What you must do before you're seated?!
Oops! That's right.
This room is enveloped by a special barrier,
so if one doesn't perform the
Holy Grail Ceremony within 66 seconds,
they'll vanish into thin air.
Precisely.
Laguz!
Well? Have you come to terms with it?
You think it's that simple?
It's like I'm trapped in a nightmare.
You say I used to be one of the A-ranked soldiers in Dark Reunion?!
After discovering their true goal was the "Mankind Sorting Plan,"
I stole the destructive stone "Panalize" from them and escaped?!
And when they cornered me, I performed the forbidden "Phantom" technique
to become a disembodied soul?!
Phantom
Then I entered the body of Shun Kaidou, still in his mother's womb?!
How do you expect me to believe that?!
You seem rather pleased.
I'm not!
It matters not. Have you started to see the truth in my words?
Well, I have long sensed that I was somehow different from others...
Your power is essential for destroying Dark Reunion.
We'll continue to assist you in regaining your lost memories.
"We"? What do you mean?
What are you saying? There are four others seated here as well...
Crimson Blade
Amber Fang
Golden
Thunderbolt
Blue Horn That Is Almost
Completely Transparent
Of course, they are all phantoms.
What? Don't tell me you can't see them.
If you can't, you're beyond hope.
O-Of course I can see them!
I meant to ask if their physical forms weren't here.
Oh, I see. You're correct. Their physical forms aren't here.
The others still don't trust you, after all.
Really?
Speaking of trust, did you complete the "Sworn Ally Absolution"?
I did just as you asked.
Oh?
I see. These answers are...
You never cease to amaze me, The Jet-Black Wings!
At this rate, you'll soon be accepted into our circle.
Really?! If that's all it takes, I'll gladly fill out as many—
Duck!
What?
Mannaz! Ingwaz! Wunjo!
Did something happen?
Dark Reunion just found out about this place!
We were just attacked.
We were?!
The four other members were all killed.
What?! Phantoms can die?!
Yes, even phantoms can die!
If we wish to live, we must act posthaste!
I'll create a stronger barrier! Lend me your aid!
Okay! What do you want me to do?!
Metal objects can interfere with the barrier.
Put any metal objects on you in that bag made of special fabric.
Okay!
Even my loose change?
Of course!
No more time! Just throw in the whole wallet!
O-Okay!
All right! Now, mimic my movements!
Got it!
Ansuz, jera!
A-Ansuz, jera!
Eihwaz!
It seems we've successfully forged the barrier.
That was close, wasn't it?
You should probably go home now.
Okay. Then can I have my metal objects back?
No, you can't. The barrier is still unstable.
It'd be risky to move them.
But my train pass is in my wallet.
Many thanks for your help today!
If not for you, I would've perished.
Excellent job, The Jet-Black Wings! You're our savior.
Of course.
Well then, come back around the same time tomorrow.
Oh, and keep working on the "Sworn Ally Absolution."
Sure.
Savior, huh? I like the sound of that.
I guess I'll bring Saiki tomorrow.
He's got eighth-grader syndrome so bad!
He didn't even realize this was just my homework!
I was just playing along with his story.
He even left his wallet here.
Good grief.
Dark Reunion, what a joke!
Thanks for doing my homework!
Kaidou...
You should choose your friends carefully. I'm telling you this as a friend.
What's going on? A blackout?
No. It's Dark Reunion.
Don't tell anyone yet, okay? This does involve the fate of the world.
Huh? It's open.
What on Earth is this?!
That's the mark of Dark Reunion!
Are they right behind me?!
Bingo.
Beachside Summer Story
Hey, pal! Let's go to the beach!
I just happened to pass by and
I saw "Saiki" on the nameplate.
So I figured this was your house.
Y-Y-Y-You're Kuu's friend?!
Da Da
Da Dum
He is not my friend.
Wah! This is the first time one of Kuu's friends has come over to visit.
I'm so happy!
Me and Saiki aren't friends.
What?
We're pals!
Wah! To think that Kuu has finally gotten a pal...
Hey, pal. I didn't know you had a big sister.
Wah! He thought I was his sister! I'm so happy!
How many times are you going to make my mom cry?
What? What? You're his mom?
That's right! So what brought you here today?
I'm off to the beach and I came to ask him to join me.
Oh, that sounds nice.
It does not. Like hell I'm going.
Your pal came all this way to get you.
You're going, Kusuo.
Wah...
SEASIDE SHOP
Restrooms
Showers
And that's how I ended up at a place like this.
Oh, I bet you can't swim, can you?
Why don't you come here, you runt?!
So Kaidou's here too?
H... Huh?! Wh-Wh-Wh-What're you saying?
I... I... I-I can swim!
Well, his eyes can at least.
Ack! Water!
He's drowning already? That takes some talent.
Are you okay?!
Don't tell me that butt is...
Oh, it's you, Hairo!
Oh, Nendou! And Saiki too?
What're you doing here?
I'm volunteering as a lifeguard.
I'm drowning!
I'm coming!
Whoa, volunteering when it's this hot?
Hey, aren't you gonna swim, pal?
Just forget I'm here.
What, is no one gonna swim?
I don't wanna swim by myself...
Okay, then! I'll go pick up some girls!
Do you know what you're saying?
Hey, have you ever looked in a mirror?!
Why don't you try walking on water?
You have better odds of pulling that off.
Guys' looks aren't important. It's all about attitude.
I'm sorry. I am physically repulsed by your face.
What? You're kidding me, right? You think you have a chance with that face?
Ever heard of a mirror? They're pretty useful. You should try one sometime.
Hey, wait!
I better not let people know I'm with him.
Those women don't know a good guy when they see one.
You're so cute, little man.
Whoa! He's so cute! How old are you? Hang out with us!
Wh-What's with you?! Go away!
Please leave.
I-I just remembered I have something to do!
S-Same here!
Are you okay?!
Hey! What'd you do that for?!
Where did my pal go? The bathroom?
When I want to be alone or have something on my mind,
I often come to the sea floor. It's a relaxing environment.
Sometimes there are some strange things lying around, but no big deal.
Pal! Where are you?!
Good grief. Looks like I didn't go deep enough.
I guess I'll go back before they start looking for me.
Look at that woman!
She's drowning! This is bad!
Kaidou! I'll go rescue her! You go get Hairo and...
We need to hurry!
Wait, you can swim?
What? Uh...
Kaidou!
H-Hey. Don't worry about me. I can go back by myself.
Shut up! I can barely feel even a couple runts like you!
All right!
Hey! What happened?!
Oh, Hairo! Good timing! Give me a hand!
Sure thing! I'll hel—
My leg cramped up!
Hairo!
You too?! What's the deal?! Geez!
Sorry.
Good grief. They're all so high-maintenance.
This is too much for you, Nendou!
Let go of me!
Shut up!
Oh, crap.
A-Are you standing on water, Nendou?!
What the hell is going on?!
Like I said, you have a better chance
of walking on water than picking up girls.
Thank you very much.
Oh hey, it's the same woman from before.
I'm sorry for being rude to you earlier.
Knowing you, I thought you'd demand something in return for saving her.
I wouldn't do something so lame.
But, if she fell in love with me, I'd have to live with it, right?
That won't happen.
What'd you say?!
No, it looks like Nendou did get an admirer...
I admire you, Riki Nendou!
I admire the way you live.
Moved
...albeit a guy.
A New School Term Starts!
The Melancholy of Nendou
Today is the first day of the new term.
Now I have to see those guys every day.
PK Academy
Hairo! You got so tanned!
I volunteered as a lifeguard at the beach.
That's amazing!
What? You've got a crush on someone?!
Are you serious, Teruhashi?!
Who is it?
Who!?
Who is it?! Tell us!
I happened to run into him during the break.
You know who I mean, right?
That definitely was no mirage.
I believe it was on August 6th.
That's a day you'll never forget, right, Saiki?
I saw you that day, Teruhashi.
What?
I believe you were with...
...Nendou.
You're way off, idiot!
What?!
I mean, I was with "Yurwei Offidjot"!
Don't you know him? He was in the world tournament.
Good grief.
Hey, Saiki. Don't you think Nendou is acting strange today?
Look who's talking.
Normally, he'd be bugging us to go get ramen or something.
True. He is acting a little strange.
Oh, this? Don't concern yourself. It's a long story.
I'm not concerned at all. You don't have to tell me about it.
That is rather annoying.
This is fishy.
It does make me wonder what's up.
Oh, you're wondering about this? Well, it all started...
Stop it! I have absolutely no interest in that.
His house isn't this way.
Something's gotta be up.
Why are you so excited about this?
And why are you so used to tailing someone?
What? What's he looking at?
Ew!
Don't tell me he likes little girls...
I don't know what he's doing, but we probably should go call the police.
He entered a shop this time.
Flower Shop Jason
A flower shop? Don't tell me he's got a girlfriend!
No, that's definitely not it.
He's looking at another girl!
Is he actually...
Either way, we should call the police first.
No, it's too early to judge. There are many people who like sunflowers.
It's also natural for people to smile when they see children.
Good point. Let's not jump to conclusions.
He's entering another shop?
Tanimura
Cake
Shop
Tanimura
Cake
Shop
Tanimura
Cake
Shop
Tanimura
Cake
Shop
Tanimura
Cake
Shop
Tanimura
Cake
Shop
Tanimura
Cake
Shop
Tanimura
Cake
Shop
Tanimura
Cake
Shop
Tanimura
Cake
Shop
Tanimura
Cake
Shop
Tanimura
Cake
Shop
Tanimura
Cake
Shop
Tanimura
Cake
Shop
Tanimura
Cake
Shop
Tanimura
Cake
Shop
Tanimura
Cakes!
They're sweet! Which means women and children love them!
A woman plus a child equals a little girl!
You're the one jumping to conclusions.
I mean, he wouldn't eat something like that, right?!
Cake
Shop
Tanimura
Sunflowers too. He clearly intends to give them to someone!
But he doesn't have a girlfriend to give them to!
So that must mean they're "bait"!
He's luring in little girls with cakes and sunflowers to kidnap them!
This
way!
Here
you go!
This
way!
Here
you go!
This
way!
Here
you go!
This
way!
Here
you go!
This
way!
Here
you go!
This
way!
Although any girl lured in by him has issues too.
Here
you go!
This
way!
Here
you go!
This
way!
Here
you go!
This
way!
Here
you go!
This
way!
Here
you go!
This
way!
Here
you go!
This
way!
Here
you go!
This
way!
Here
you go!
This
way!
Here
you go!
This
way!
Here
you go!
This
way!
Here
you go!
This
way!
Here
you go!
This
way!
Here
you go!
This
way!
Here
you go!
This
way!
Here
you go!
This
way!
Here
you go!
This
way!
Here
you go!
This
way!
Here
you go!
This
way!
Here
you go!
This
way!
Here
you go!
This
way!
Here
you go!
This
way!
Here
you go!
This
way!
Here
you go!
This
way!
Here
you go!
This
way!
Here
you go!
This
way!
Here
you go!
This
way!
Here
you go!
This
way!
Here
you go!
This
way!
Here
you go!
This
way!
Here
you go!
This
way!
Here
you go!
This
way!
Here
you go!
This
way!
Here
you go!
This
way!
Here
you go!
This
way!
Here
you go!
This
way!
Here
you go!
This
way!
Here
you go!
This
way!
Here
you go!
This
way!
Here
you go!
This
way!
Here
you go!
This
way!
Here
you go!
This
way!
Here
you go!
This
way!
Here
you go!
This
way!
Here
you go!
This
way!
Here
you go!
This
way!
Cake
Shop
Tanimura
Geez... They were out of shortcake.
Oh well. It's not like anyone will actually eat it.
If no one will eat it, then it must be bait!
Nendou!
I'm disappointed in you, Nendou!
To think that you'd harm helpless little girls!
So it actually does make a "pop, pop" sound.
Hold on a sec. Aren't you guys misunderstanding something?
Visiting a grave?
Nendou Family Grave
Yeah, my dad's. Today is the anniversary of his death.
Then the sunflowers and cake...
They're offerings, of course.
It's common sense to bring flowers and snacks when visiting a grave.
Getting lectured by Nendou on common sense...
Oh, I see. He wasn't looking at little girls in a perverted way.
Those scenes made him think of his own dad.
What a misleading face.
When did your dad die?
Well, it was before I was born.
He died trying to save a girl who ran out into the street.
Maybe he was into little girls!
Uh... Well...
We really had it wrong.
B-But if it was before you were born, then he must've died really young.
Yeah. I think he was 18 or 19.
Wanna see a picture? I have one in my wallet.
What?! This is just you, isn't it?!
I know, he looks like me, right?
Mom keeps saying that I look more like him every year too.
No, it's more than that!
I've seen Nendou's father's photo before,
but they really look surprisingly similar.
It's just his dad has a scar over his right eye instead of his left.
Yeah, just like this.
That was... a trick of light, right?
Hey! Let's go get some ramen!
I know I'm pretty unreal myself,
but I don't believe in things like ghosts.
I'll just put today out of my mind.
Saiki
It's for me? That's unusual.
To Mr. Kusuo Saiki
I know that you are
a psychic.
To Mr. Kusuo Saiki
I know that you are
a psychic.
To Mr. Kusuo Saiki
I know that you are
a psychic.
To Mr. Kusuo Saiki
I know that you are
a psychic.
To Mr. Kusuo Saiki
I know that you are
a psychic.
To Mr. Kusuo Saiki
I know that you are
a psychic.
To Mr. Kusuo Saiki
I know that you are
a psychic.
To Mr. Kusuo Saiki
I know that you are
a psychic.
To Mr. Kusuo Saiki
I know that you are
a psychic.
To Mr. Kusuo Saiki
I know that you are
a psychic.
To Mr. Kusuo Saiki
I know that you are
a psychic.
To Mr. Kusuo Saiki
I know that you are
a psychic.
To Mr. Kusuo Saiki
I know that you are
a psychic.
To Mr. Kusuo Saiki
I know that you are
a psychic.
To Mr. Kusuo Saiki
I know that you are
a psychic.
To Mr. Kusuo Saiki
I know that you are
a psychic.
To Mr. Kusuo Saiki
I know that you are
a psychic.
To Mr. Kusuo Saiki
I know that you are
a psychic.
To Mr. Kusuo Saiki
I know that you are
a psychic.
To Mr. Kusuo Saiki
I know that you are
a psychic.
To Mr. Kusuo Saiki
I know that you are
a psychic.
What?
We too have a psychic gift of our own
Our talent is lying dormant inside of us
How fantastic would it be if we could make it work this time
But worst-case is a disaster we can only sigh over
Wow!
Still we never gave up
We put forth our hard evidence
If we just believe and wish for it
Can our daydreams and fantasies all come to life?
"Success blooms, dreams are priceless."
"Make me happy, hey you, give it a try."
"Oh no, just try, I want to understand."
That's right, I like you!
The secret is everyone has the power to make their dreams come true
We didn't get where we are on chance or luck
Let's show the world all the wishes we can't say out loud
We have a premonition coming, the signs cropping up in reality
Our future is in our hands
So let's start again!
Preview
The story ends on a cliffhanger
right after I got a surprise letter...
But don't worry. That's how it went in the manga too.
Next time on The Disastrous Life of Saiki K. the anime...
I'll keep knocking out an episode for each manga chapter.